Guide to the Lindseth collection of American woman suffrage,[ca. 1820-1920].
Lindseth collection of American woman suffrage,[ca. 1820-1920]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Lindseth collection of American woman suffrage, [ca. 1820-1920].
8002
Jon A., Lindseth
ca. 500 items.
Correspondence, Memorabilia, Printed Materials, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection includes rare books, periodicals, pamphlets, broadsides, convention leaflets, letters, cartoons, photographs, banners, campaign buttons, and other objects.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection includes rare books, periodicals, pamphlets, broadsides, convention leaflets, letters, cartoons, photographs, banners, campaign buttons, and other objects. Highlights of the collection include campaign literature produced by suffrage organizations such as the National American Woman Suffrage Association, the Congressional Union for Woman Suffrage, and the Empire State Campaign Committee, and the writings of prominent women activists Jane Addams, Susan B. Anthony, Alice Stone Blackwell, Carrie Chapman Catt, Maria Weston Chapman, Caroline Dall, Mary Abigail Dodge, Abigail Scott Duniway, Margaret Fuller, Charlotte Perkins Gilman, Angelina and Sarah Grimké, Ida Husted Harper, Julia Ward Howe, Mary Putnam Jacobi, Mary Livermore, Lucretia Mott, Sylvia Pankhurst, Alice Paul, Jannette Rankin, Anna Howard Shaw, Elizabeth Cady Stanton, Lucy Stone and Frances Willard. The collection also contains Margaret Fuller's personal copy of Goethe's Werke, an inscribed edition of Charlotte Perkins Gilman's The Yellow Wall Paper, and several letters by suffrage leaders Susan B. Anthony, Carrie Chapman Catt, Margaret Fuller, Charlotte Perkins Gilman, Julia Ward Howe, Lucretia Mott, Alice Paul, Anna Howard Shaw, and Lucy Stone.
While the majority of the collection documents the work of pro-suffrage forces, also present are a number of publications arguing against universal suffrage, such as leaflets distributed by the Woman's Anti-Suffrage Society, and the New York State Association Opposed to Woman Suffrage. The collection also contains issues of scarce women's magazines that were published in support of the suffrage movement, such as The Revolution, The Suffragist, The Woman Citizen, and Woodhull and Clafin's Weekly.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Lindseth, Jon A.,; Addams, Jane, 1860-1935.; Anthony, Susan B.(Susan Brownell), 1820-1906.; Blackwell, Alice Stone, 1857-1950.; Catt, Carrie Chapman, 1859-1947.; Chapman, Maria Weston, 1806-1885.; Dall, Caroline Wells Healey, 1822-1912.; Dodge, Mary Abigail, 1833-1896.; Duniway, Abigail Scott, 1834-1915.; Fuller, Margaret, 1810-1850.; Gilman, Charlotte Perkins, 1860-1935.; Grimké, Angelina Emily, 1805-1879.; Grimké, Sarah Moore, 1792-1873.; Harper, Ida Husted, 1851-1931.; Howe, Julia Ward, 1819-1910.; Jacobi, Mary Putnam, 1842-1906.; Livermore, Mary Ashton Rice, 1820-1905.; Mott, Lucretia, 1793-1880.; Pankhurst, E. Sylvia(Estelle Sylvia), 1882-1960.; Paul, Alice, 1885-1977.; Rankin, Jeannette, 1880-1973.; Shaw, Anna Howard, 1847-1919.; Stanton, Elizabeth Cady, 1815-1902.; Stone, Lucy, 1818-1893.; Willard, Frances Elizabeth, 1839-1898.; National American Woman Suffrage Association.; Congressional Union for Woman Suffrage.; Empire State Campaign Committee.; New York State Association Opposed to the Extension of Suffrage to Women.
Titles:
Revolution (New York, N.Y.); Suffragist (Washington, D.C.); Woman's journal.; Woman citizen.; Woodhull and Claflin's weekly.
Subjects:
Women--Suffrage--United States.; Women--Suffrage--Great Britain.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Printed Materials
Boxes: 1-5
Series II. Manuscripts
Boxes: 6, 7
Series III. Pins & Ribbons
Boxes: 8
Series IV. Graphics
Boxes: 9, 10
Series V. Bound Manuscripts
Series VI. Artifacts
Box 14
Series VII. Videocassettes
Series VIII. Additional Manuscript Materials
Boxes: 11-13
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Printed Materials
  - Empire State Campaign Committee: "A million women appeal to the voters of New York for justice". NY: ESCC., [1917]; S-005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Curtis, George William: "Equal rights for all". Rochester, NY: NY State Constitutional Convention Campaign., 1867; S-010 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gladstone, William E.: "Female suffrage". [S.l.]: American Women Remonstrants., 1892; S-011 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Blake, Lillie Devereux [et al]. "Report of hearing before the Committee on Woman Suffrage, January 28, 1896". Washington, DC: GPO., 1896; S-012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Addams, Jane: "Why women should vote". NY: National American Woman Suffrage Association., [1912]; S-016 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Guild, Mary [et al]: "First annual report of the Massachusetts Association opposed to the extension of suffrage to women". Boston., 1896; S-017 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Woman's Journal: "Eminent opinions on woman suffrage", leaflet, vol. vi, no. 1. Boston: Office of the Woman's Journal., 1893; S-018 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Thomas, Mary Bentley: "Testimony from the governors of the four free states"., [c. 1910]; S-019 / S-176 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Willard, Frances E.: "The ballot for the home. Reasons for woman's enfranchisement". Boston: American Woman Suffrage Association., 1888; S-020 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins: "Charlotte Perkins Gilman, Writer and lecturer" [Broadside]. NY: Charlton Company., [1915]; S-027 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - National American Woman Suffrage Association: "Votes for women". NY: NAWSA., [c. 1910]; S-031 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - National American Woman Suffrage Association: "About voting". NY: NAWSA., [c. 1893, before 1917]; S-032 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - National Woman's Party: "National Woman's Party". Washington, DC: National Woman's Party., 1922; S-069 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - National American Woman Suffrage Association: "Fruits of Equal Suffrage, II". Warren, OH: National American Woman Suffrage Association., [c. 1890s]; S-076 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts State Woman Suffrage Party: "Who shares the cost of war?". Boston: Massachusetts State Woman Suffrage Association., [1920]; S-077 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins: Some new lectures [Promotional piece]. NY: Gilman., [c. 1900]; S-095 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins: Charlotte Perkins Gilman promotional flyer. NY: James B. Pond, "The Pond Bureau"., [c. 1924]; S-096 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Howe, Julia Ward: "The uses of victory", Register Tract New Series, No. 1. Boston: Christian Register Association., 1898; S-099 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mott, Lucretia: "A sermon to the medical students". Philadelphia: Merrihew & Thompson., 1849; S-104 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins: Books by Charlotte Perkins Gilman [Broadside]. Boston: Small, Maynard & Co.; NY: Charlton Co., [after 1898]; S-106 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins: Charlotte Perkins Gilman, Author and lecturer. [Promotional piece]. Norwich Town, CT: Gilman., [c. 1900]; S-107 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins: "A Gilman Week". NY: Charlton Co., [after 1916]; S-108 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins: "In this our world". Boston: Small, Maynard & Company., 1898; S-109 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins: Studies in social philosophy. [NY]: Gamut Club., [c. 1900]; S-110 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Howe, Julia Ward: Suffrage song handbill. [S.l.]: [National American Woman Suffrage Association]., [c. 1895]; S-111 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Tilton, Theodore: Biography of Victoria C. Woodhull. NY: Golden Age., 1871; S-112 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - New York State Woman Suffrage Party: "What President Wilson Says". NY: NYSWSP., [c. 1917]; S-117 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - New York State Woman Suffrage Party: "Suffrage as a war measure". NYC: NYSWSP., October 1917; S-118 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Congressional Union for Woman Suffrage: "Come to the Capitol". [Broadside]. Washington, DC: Congressional Union for Woman Suffrage., [c. 1916]; S-122 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Congressional Union for Woman Suffrage: Itinerary of the "Suffrage Special". Washington, DC: Congressional Union for Woman Suffrage., 1916; S-124 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Congressional Union for Woman Suffrage: Woman's Party Convention, Chicago, June 5, 6, and 7th. Chicago: CUWS., [1916]; S-126 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth: "Woman and her wishes: an essay". NY: Fowlers and Wells., 1853; S-128 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Stevens, Doris: "Tribute to Alva Belmont". Washington, DC: Inter American Commission of Women, [c. 1933]; S-130 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Harper, Ida Husted: "The life & work of Susan B. Anthony". Rochester, NY: M. D. Fenner., [c. 1898]; S-131 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bicknell, Thomas W.: "Victory"., 1920; S-140 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Abbott, Mrs. Lyman: "Mrs. Lyman Abbott on Woman Suffrage". Albany, NY., [c. 1900]; S-141 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Addams, Jane: 'To the women voters of the United States from the women in political bondage'. New York: Stoddard-Sutherland Press., 1912; S-150 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dennett, Mary Ware: 'The real point'. NY: National American Woman Suffrage Association., [c. 1912-1917]; S-151 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Henry, Josephine R. & Annah Robinson Watson: 'The new woman of the new south & The attitude of southern women on the suffrage question'. Boston: Arena, Vol. 11., February 1895; S-152 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - McCulloch, Catharine Waugh: 'Shall men vote?', [c. 1912-1917]; S-153 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Michigan Equal Suffrage Association: 'A plain talk to workingmen on a Square Deal'. Grand Rapids, MI: Michigan Equal Suffrage Association., [c. 1912-1917]; S-154 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - New Jersey Woman Suffrage Association: "True democracy" & "Plain facts for the working man". Plainfield, NJ: New Jersey Woman Suffrage Association., [c. 1915]; S-156 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Empire State Campaign Committee: "Ours is a government ...". NY: Empire State Campaign Committee., 1915; S-157 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association: Small Archive of Suffrage Material. Harrisburg, PA: Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association. 1 broadside: 'Woman's Liberty Bell', [c. 1915]; S-158 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association: Small Archive of Suffrage Material. Harrisburg, PA: Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association. 1 broadside: 'Women are Citizens', [c. 1915]; S-158 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Addams, Jane: 'Why women should vote'. Harrisburg, PA: Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association, 2 copies. Cf: Listed as part of the Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association Small Archive [folders 8-11], [1914-1915]; S-340 / S-158 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association: Small Archive of Suffrage Material. Harrisburg, PA: Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association, 1 postcard., [c. 1915]; S-158 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Reynolds, Minnie J.: "Votes for women a success". NY: National American Woman Suffrage Association., 1913; S-159 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Harper, Ida Husted: "The passing of Anna Howard Shaw". NY: National Woman Suffrage Publishing Co., Inc., July 1919; S-160 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - South Dakota Universal Franchise League: "Isn't it true?". Huron, SD: South Dakota Universal Franchise League., [c. 1912-1915]; S-161 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Anthony, Susan B. & Elizabeth Cady Stanton: 80th birthday ephemera. Washington, DC: "Greetings" by Mrs. Blatch., February 15, 1900; S-168 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Anthony, Susan B. & Elizabeth Cady Stanton: 80th birthday ephemera. Washington, DC: 1900, February 15. Poem by Elizabeth Cady Stanton., February 15, 1900; S-168 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Massachusetts Woman Suffrage: "Votes for Women! The woman's reason because ...". Boston: Libbie Printing Co., [c. 1910]; S-172 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Burr, Frances Ellen: Address delivered before the legislative committee on woman suffrage in the Connecticut House of Representatives., March 2, 1887; S-173 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Taylor, Edward T.: "A word to the wise". NY: Empire State Campaign Committee., 1912; S-175 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Women's Anti-Suffrage Association: "Woman suffrage and the liquor question. Facts show women's votes have NOT aided prohibition." NYC: Women's Anti-Suffrage Association., July 1, 1915; S-177 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady: "Address in favor of universal suffrage, for the election of delegates to the Constitutional Convention." Albany, NY: Weed, Parsons and Company., 1867; S-178 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Cincinnati and Hamilton County Association: "Why we do not approve of woman suffrage." Cincinnati, OH: Cincinnati & Hamilton County Association., [c. 1915]; S-184 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Anonymous: "Woman suffrage resolutions"., [c. 1875]; S-202 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Lindsey, Judge Ben & George Creel: "Measuring up results of equal suffrage in Colorado". Pasadena, CA: Citizens Suffrage League., [c. 1911]; S-204 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Shaw, Anna Howard: "Your great opportunity to hear ... Dr. Anna Howard Shaw ... and the Hon. Wm. H. Wadhams ...". [NY: s.n.], [1917]; S-205 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - New York State Woman Suffrage Party: "Garden primer: how to plant and care for a vegetable garden". NYC: Mayor Mitchel's Food Supply Committee., April 1917; S-206 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - New York State Woman Suffrage Party: "Don't forget to vote for woman suffrage first". NY: New York State Woman Suffrage Party., [1917]; S-207 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - New York State Woman Suffrage Party: "To the voters resolution adopted by the NY State Woman Suffrage Party Conference, Saratoga, August 30th, 1917". NYC: NYSWSP., 1917; S-208 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Shaw, Anna Howard: "Anna Howard Shaw Memorial of the National American Woman Suffrage Association"., [1920]; S-210 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Taylor, A. Elizabeth: "A short history of the woman suffrage movement in Tennessee". Nashville, TN: Vanderbilt University., 1943; S-219 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Empire State Campaign Committee: "The next president". NY: Empire State Campaign Committee., [1915]; S-223 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Ormondroyd, Joan (Compiler): "Women's Suffrage History, Rights, Equality, Liberation. Part 1". Ithaca: Cornell University., 1972; S-249 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Catt, Carrie Chapman: "Freedom Agenda". NY: Carrie Chapman Catt Memorial Fun, Inc., June 1955; S-270 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Webster, Dr. George W.: "A physiological basis for the shorter working day for women". Washington, DC: GPO., 1921; S-271 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Jonathan: "The married women's statues, and their results upon divorce and society". Clinton, MA: Clinton Printing Co., 1884; S-284 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Massachusetts Man Suffrage Association: "Is it expedient that municipal suffrage be granted to women?". Boston: MMSA., [c. 1880]; S-288 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Stafford, Windell Phillips: "My reasons for favoring equal suffrage". Burlington, VT: Equal Franchise League., [c. 1920]; S-291 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Crocker, George G.: "Argument of Hon. George G. Crocker, at the hearing before the Committee on Woman Suffrage, January 29, 1884"., 1884; S-298 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Harper, Ida Husted: "A brief history of the movement for woman suffrage in the United States". NY: National Woman Suffrage Publishing Co., Inc., January 1917; S-308 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Woman's Journal: "To suffrage clubs and leagues". Boston: [Woman's Journal], Januar 19, 1889; S-309 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - National Woman Suffrage Publishing Co., Inc.: "Who represents her?". Plainfield, NJ: National Woman Suffrage Publishing Co., Inc., [c. 1917]; S-310 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Blackwell, Alice Stone: "Do teachers need the ballot?". NY" National Woman Suffrage Publishing Co., Inc., [1916-1917]; S-311 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Addams, Jane: "Women and public housing". NY: National Woman Suffrage Publishing Co., Inc., [1916-1917]; S-312 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - South Dakota Universal Franchise League: "Testimony from Wyoming". Huron, SD: SDUFL., [1901]; S-313 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bjorkman, Frances M. (Editor): "Where women vote". NY" National American Woman Suffrage Association., 1914; S-315 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - National Woman Suffrage Publishing Co.: "What every woman knows". NY: National Woman Suffrage Publishing Co., [1916-1917]; S-316 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Shredded Wheat Company: "Votes for women" advertisement. Niagara Falls, NY: Shredded Wheat Company., [1913]; S-338 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - National American Woman Suffrage Association: "Woman suffrage addresses and pageant-tableau". NY: Theatre Magazine., [1913]; S-377 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Beaman, Fernando C.: "Reconstruction and impartial suffrage speech". Washington, DC: Office of the Great Republic., 1868; S-424 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Pepsin Syrup Co.: "Famous women of the world". Monticello, IL: Pepsin Syrup Co., 1918; S-436 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Catt, Carrie Chapman: "The winning policy"., [c. 1916]; S-379 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - "Woman Suffrage Resolutions". [Broadside on newsprint], [c. 1875]; S-439 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Root, Elihu: "Address delivered by the Hon. Elihu root before the New York State Constitutional Convention, on August 15th, 1894". NY: New York State Association opposed to Woman Suffrage., 1894; S-446 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Blackwell, Alice Stone: "Progress of equal rights", Political Equality Series, Vol. III, no. 12. NY: National American Woman Suffrage Association., 1899; S-447 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - National American Woman Suffrage Association: "Congressional reports in favor on an amendment to the National Constitution prohibiting the disfranchisement of United States Citizens on account of sex". NY" NAWSA., [1893]; S-450 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - National American Woman Suffrage Association: "Testimonials from prominent persons concerning the operation of woman suffrage in Wyoming, Colorado, and Utah". NY: NAWSA., [1897-1900]; S-451 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - May, Charles S.: "Equal suffrage speech". Kalamazoo, MI., 1868; S-456 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Daly, Mary L.: "The suffragists' 'America'". Yonkers, NY: Allied Printing., [c. 1915-1917]; S-460 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Davis, Alph Briggs: "Woman: the hope of the world. A poem". Worcester and Clinton, MA: Independent Tract Society., 1875; S-467 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - National American Women Suffrage Association: "Catholic opinions". NY: National Woman Suffrage Publishing Co., Inc., [1915-1917]; S-469 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Hooker, Mrs. D. R.: "The Connecticut Players in 'How the vote was won: a one-act farce by Cecily Hamilton and Christopher St. John". Norwich, CT: Bulletin Print., 1913; S-470 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Pethick-Lawrence, Mrs. Emmeline: "Some American impressions of an English suffragist". [S.l.]: Majority Printery., [1914]; S-472 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - National American Women Suffrage Association: "Women suffrage and the liquor interests. Some exhibits". NY: National Woman Suffrage Publishing Co., Inc., February 1916; S-452 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Rankin, Jeannette. Small Archive: Campaign button, pamphlets, leaflets, mimeographed letter., S-463 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Flyer: How to vote for Woman Suffrage Amendment, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Series II. Manuscripts
  - Anthony, Susan B.: ALS twice. Washington, D.C.: Susan B. Anthony., April 14, 1884; S-180 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Anthony, Susan B.: APS, to E[ugene] V[ictor] Debs. Cambridge: [s.n.], February 10, 1879; S-252 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Anthony, Susan B.: ALS to Mr. Jan Neuthusen. Rochester, NY: [s.n.], March 22, 1899; S-091 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - [Anthony, Susan B.]: Broadside with Anthony's autograph notation. [S.l.]: Official Board, Indiana National Woman Suffrage., 1887; S-090 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Anthony, Susan B.: TLS to "My dear friend". Rochester, NY: [s.n., October 1, 1888; S-089 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Anthony, Susan B.: TLS to Mrs. Carrie Chapman Catt. [Rochester, NY: s.n.], June 17, [1897]; S-055 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bjorkman, Frances M. (Editor): Woman suffrage history arguments and results. NY: National American Woman Suffrage Assn., 1913; S-147 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Blackwell, Alice Stone: Signed document: stock certificate for five shares. Boston: [s.n.], June 7, 1911; S-079 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Catt, Carrie Chapman: TLS to Mr. John G. Saxe. NY: Empire State Campaign Committee., July 14, 1914; S-376 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Chapman, Maria Weston: Corrected galley proof for an unidentified work. [S.l.: s.n.], July 2, 1885; S-092 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Chase, Mrs. Salmon P.: Suffrage speech [unsigned]. [S.l.]: Mrs. Salmon P. Chase., [c. 1880]; S-337 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Croly, Jane Cunningham: ALS to an unidentified lady. NY., February 29, 1896; S-086 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fuller, [Sarah] Margaret: ALS to Mrs. [Abigail Clark] Stimson. Cambridge, MA., March 16, 1844; S-004 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins: APS. Cincinnati, OH: [s.n.], [November 2], 1913; S-058 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins: ALS to Mrs. Swift. Norwich Town, CT., December 8, 1924; S-006 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Grimke, Sarah and Lucy Stone: Canceled check. Boston., January 1, 1872; S-007 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Harper, Frances Ellen Watkins: AVS--autograph verse signed., [c. 1895]; S-054 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Hebard, Grace Raymond: TLS suffrage letter to Mrs. Townsend Scott. Laramie, WY., May 25, 1916; S-123 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Holt, C. M.: "Woman suffrage" manuscript. Holograph MSS ... ink faded., [c. 1880]; S-449 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Howe, Julia Ward: Remarks on the New England Women's Club. Boston., [c. 1880-1895]; S-378 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Howe, Julia Ward: Autograph mss of "Battle Hymn of the Republic"., [c. 1885]; S-132 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Howe, Julia Ward: Miss Mary Big' low., [c. 1850]; S-129 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Howe, Julia Ward: Three ALS to Josephine Chester, [c.1884], August 9, September 2, 1885. Boston., [c. 1885]; S-061 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Howe, Julia Ward: ALS. Newport, RI., September 2, 1885; S-059 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Howe, Julia Ward: ALS. 241 Beacon Street: To Mrs. Bridgman. Boston., April 11, 1897; S-062 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Livermore, Mary: Autograph Sentiment Signed. Melrose, MA., May 26, 1895; S-063 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Mott, Lucretia: ALS to M. & E. Moore. Philadelphia., June 26, 1842; S-064 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Mott, Lucretia: ALS to W[illia]m L[loyd] & Helen Garrison. Auburn, NY., August 31, 1852; S-065 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - National Woman's Party: TLS seeking pledge of support to Mrs. C.A. Baldwin. Colorado Springs, CO: National Woman's Party., February 15, 1917; S-369 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Paul, Alice: Western Union Telegram. Chicago., May 29, 1916; S-127 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Paul, Alice: TLS to Mrs. Annette McCrea. Washington, D.C., February 1, 1917; S-082 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Paul, Alice: TLS to Mrs. Annette McCrea. Washington, D.C., March 26, 1917; S-083 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Reynolds, Alice L.: ALS to Mrs. [Townsend] Scott. Near Evanston, WY., June 6, 1916; S-179 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Robinson, Harriet: First Woman Suffrage Ballot in Massachusetts. Middlesex County, MA., [1876]; S-081 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Shaw, Anna Howard: TLS to Professor Herbert T. Stephens, Kansas City University, Kansas City, Kansas. NY., March 13, 1913; S-084 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Stone, Lucy and Henry Blackwell: Canceled check payable to Lucy Stone. Boston., December 21, 1891; S-248 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Stone, Lucy: ALS to Mrs. Murray. Newark, NJ., December 7, 1868; S-066 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Willard, Frances Elizabeth: TLS to F. E. Abbot. London., January 27, 1893; S-068 (Box 7, Folder 20)